(Sheldon:)Here you go.
(Sheldon:)This is now the only lab with glassware
washed by a man with two doctorates...
(Sheldon:)...and a restraining order
signed by Carl Sagan.
Soap spots. Wash them again.
(Sheldon:)You're being ridiculous.
Those are perfectly clean.
(Amy:)This beaker used to contain
cerebrospinal fluid...
(Amy:)...from an elephant
that died of syphilis.
(Amy:)If it's, in fact, perfectly clean,
drink from it.
(Sheldon:)Biologists are mean.
(Amy:)Perhaps this task
will be a little bit more up your alley.
(Amy:)I need you to count the bacteria spores
on these petri dishes.
(Sheldon:)There was something wrong
with that detergent.
(Sheldon:)- That was way too bubbly.
- I'm sure it was.
(Sheldon:)I intend to write that soap company
a strongly-worded letter.
(Amy:)Yeah, good for you.
Now start counting.
(Sheldon:)You know what this place needs?
(Sheldon:)A suggestion box.